Finding Aid for the Reverend James M. Lawson, Jr. Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Funerals (1975-1981)
  Funerals – October 15, 1977 – Leona Smith Reed
  Funerals – October 29, 1977 – Lisa Elaine Luck
  Funerals – December 2, 1977 – Lionel Briggs
  Funerals – December 8, 1977 – Charlie Wilkerson
  Funerals – January 13, 1978 – Kenneth Hayden Denton
  Funerals – June 3, 1978 – Sam L. Manor
  Funerals – October 10, 1978 – Winfred Skillman
  Funerals – November 8, 1978 – Laura Adeline Winston
  Funerals – November 16, 1978 – Charlyne W. Thompson
  Funerals – January 5, 1979 – Carl G. and Heloise J. Hall
  Funerals – February 7, 1979 – Elise January Turner
  Funerals – March 16, 1979 – Mary Lucille Washington
  Funerals – May 5, 1979 – Preston L. Griffin
  Funerals – July 20, 1979 – Samuel Young
  Funerals – October 15, 1979 – Allene L. Saunders
  Funerals – October 23, 1979 – Rafe Edward Adams
  Funerals – November 12, 1979 – Annie Pearl Lockett
  Funerals – November 21, 1979 – Mildred Marie Vaughn
  Funerals – June 23, 1980 – Cyrus Lee McPherson, Jr.
  Funerals – December 31, 1980 – Eermson Knight
  Funerals – January 31, 19811 – Arnold K. Cameron, Dr.
  Funerals – February 17, 1981 – Theodore Winfield Payne, Jr.
  Funerals – February 18, 1981 – Wardia Nichols Cravens
  Funerals – March 28, 1981 – Mildred M. Denton
  Funerals – June 22, 1981 – Julius E. Penn, Jr.
  Funerals – June 28, 1981 - Ina P. Howard
  Funerals – July 13, 1981 – Arthur V. Seay
  Funerals – August 7, 1981 – Robert S. Lawery
  Funerals – August 22, 1981 – Michael Thomas
  Funerals – August 28, 1981 – Mary Sylvia Newton Harris
  Funerals – December 19, 1981 – Alberta Elizabeth Evans
- Funerals (1982-1986)
  Funerals – January 13, 1982 – Ronald Francis Fegan
  Funerals – January 23, 1982 – Hattie Irene Bailey
  Funerals – march 5, 1982 – Warren Hobson Woodruff
  Funerals – March 3, 1982 – Robert Lee Billups, Jr.
  Funerals – April 12, 1982 – Ethel Marie Holmes Jackson
  Funerals – May 5, 1982 – James Henry Jones, Jr.
  Funerals – May 7, 1982 – Georgia Mae Brown
  Funerals – May 19, 1982 – Leonard Baker
  Funerals – September 27, 1982 – James Edwin Reid
  Funerals – October 6, 1982 – Parker Gardner
  Funerals – October 30, 1982 – Dallas H. Veil
  Funerals – November 29, 1982 – Viola Dennis
  Funerals – December 3, 1982 – William (Bill) Davis
  Funerals – February 18, 1983 – Cleopatra Johnson
  Funerals – March 9, 1983 – James Edward Pace
  Funerals – March 26, 1983 – Clarence I. Parker, Jr.
  Funerals – May 19, 1983 – R.T. “Robbie” Robinson
  Funerals – June 27, 1983 – Arthur Lee Pittman, Jr.
  Funerals – June 29, 1983 – Mark Albert DeCosta
  Funerals – July 2, 1983 – Percy B. Elliott
  Funerals – February 11, 1984 – James Robert Jones
  Funerals – February 1984 – Harold Joshua Jackson
  Funerals – March 28, 1984 – Virgil Dean Williams, Jr.
  Funerals – April 6, 1984 – Neston Woodrow Williams
  Funerals – April 14, 1984 – Harriette F. Plummer
  Funerals – April 18, 1984 – Idella Luvenia Johnson
  Funerals – April 28, 1984 – Alma Frederica Freeman
  Funerals – June 12, 1984 – Samuel Daniel Kane
  Funerals – July 24, 1984 – Vivian Hortense Jones Wormley
  Funerals – September 1, 1984 – Joe Rodgers, Jr.
  Funerals – October 27, 1984 – Lloyd Victor Brown
  Funerals – November 23, 1984 – Therman L. Hines
  Funerals – November 28, 1984 – Bishop Charles Franklin Golden
  Funerals – December 18, 1984 – Don Albert Mosby
  Funerals – February 6, 1985 – Edgar Rollins Edwards
  Funerals – February 9, 1985 – Ventie Moore “Bob” Robinson
  Funerals – March 7, 1985 – Alvin F. Payne
  Funerals – March 23, 1985 – Myrtle Knox Burgess
  Funerals – April 29, 1985 – Lily Mae McKellon
  Funerals – August 16, 1985 – Sabrina Anna Polk
  Funerals – August 24, 1985 – Ruth Geraldine Lipscomb Robinson
  Funerals – September 4, 1985 – Beulah Lee Honore
  Funerals – September 6, 1985 – Lula Bolden Evans
  Funerals – September 1, 1985 – Ruth Margene Shoals
  Funerals – September 14, 1985 – Bernice W. Barnum
  Funerals – September 26, 1985 – Glenn Allen Weaver
  Funerals – October 29, 1985 – Anna Mae Smith
  Funerals – November 1, 1985 – Adelia Agatha Brown
  Funerals - November 2, 1985 – Scott Collins Jamison
  Funerals – January 17, 1986 – Edith Brooks Brown
  Funerals – May 12, 1986 – Lula “Louise” Carrington
  Funerals – July 26, 1986 – Stella W. Wiggins
  Funerals – August 4, 1986 – Ernestine T. Reid
  Funerals – August 5, 1986 – Minnie Stewart
  Funerals – August 23, 1986 – Isabel Margaret Hairston
  Funerals – September 9, 1986 – Hilma Karlene Jenkins
  Funerals – September 13, 1986 – Gertell Wilhelmina Campbell
  Funerals – December 11, 1986 – Roselle Ivory Gayle, Jr.
- Funerals (1987-1990)
  Funerals – April 16, 1987 – Lela Bell Shockley
  Funerals – April 28, 1987 – LaDell Rachaum McCarther
  Funerals – August 8, 1987 – Geraldine Juliette Smith
  Funerals – December 1, 1987 – Millicent Elmira Hendy
  Funerals – December 4, 1987 – Delta Mae Adams
  Funerals – January 25, 1988 – Augusta Saunders
  Funerals – February 12, 1988 – Flora Watson Moore
  Funerals – February 29, 1988 – Thirkfield Ellis Cravens, Sr.
  Funerals – May 14, 1988 – Jean Morman Collins
  Funerals – June 8, 1988 – Ethel Walker
  Funerals – June 13, 1988 – Arthur L. Stephens
  Funerals – July 21, 1988 – Esell Agnes Littlejohn
  Funerals – July 25, 1988 – Hubert Hammond
  Funerals – August 6, 1988 – Charles T. Prime
  Funerals – August 9, 1988 – Naomi Collins
  Funerals – August 16, 1988 – Anna M. Jackson
  Funerals – October 3, 1988 – Charles Andrew Taylor
  Funerals – October 10, 1988 – Elouise “Undine” Clark
  Funerals – October 12, 1988 – Donzella W. Marshall
  Funerals – November 3, 1988 – Bernard Thomas Roberts
  Funerals – November 18, 1988 – L. L. White
  Funerals – January 20, 1989 – William B. Page
  Funerals – January 24, 1989 – Wright Fillmore
  Funerals – January 26, 1989 – Cornelius Nathaniel Bradford
  Funerals – February 22, 1989 – Eartha Tarver
  Funerals – April 14, 1989 – J. Cullen Fentress
  Funerals – June 28, 1989 – Gilbert Nettles Curry
  Funerals – August 30, 1989 – Henry Joseph Monroe
  Funerals – September 18, 1989 – Sarah Elizabeth McDonald
  Funerals – December 26, 1989 – Roselyn Morgan
  Funerals - February 12, 199 – Mack C. Riggsbee
  Funerals – February 17, 1990 – Jessie B. Byres
  Funerals – April 14, 1990 – Neva Gilmore Wright
  Funerals – May 29, 1990 – Jane Elizabeth Allen
  Funerals – June 18, 1990 – Michael Noel Broady
  Funerals – June 20, 1990 – Gardenia Elmira Johnson Hill
  Funerals – June 23, 1990 – George W. Davis III
  Funerals – July 12, 1990 – Pearl Spears Taylor
  Funerals – August 4, 1990 – Vernon C. Rose
  Funerals – August 23, 1990 – Corene G. Baker
  Funerals – September 7, 1990 – James Walter Middleton
  Funerals – October 20, 1990 – Theodore Franklin Fain
  Funerals – October 30, 1990 – Kathryn B. Marsalis
  Funerals – November 12, 1990 – Crystal Frances Albright Marshall
  Funerals – December 18, 1990 – Carrie Lee Dumas
  Funerals – December 21, 1990 – Pearl C. Fortune
  Funerals – December 26, 1990 – Grace Eggleston Graham
- Funerals (1991-1992)
  Funerals – January 5, 1991 – Irma Jewel Owens
  Funerals – January 24, 1991 – Mildred Fulbright
  Funerals – January 25, 1991 – Carrie Louise Williams
  Funerals – January 31, 1991 – Louis Wellington Cosey
  Funerals – February 25, 1991 – Maggie Osborne Smith
  Funerals – March 9, 1991 – Edna M. Humes
  Funerals – March 21, 1991 – Joseph Henry Hargrove
  Funerals – March 28, 1991 – Curtis Azoras Burke
  Funerals – April 1, 1991 – Paul Leon Gayten
  Funerals – April 20, 1991 – Mattie Mae Hardy
  Funerals – April 24, 1991 – Gus Biggins
  Funerals – May 25, 1991 – Eric Earl Owens
  Funerals – May 29, 1991 – Thomas Isaac Greene
  Funerals – June 4, 1991 – Earlean Priscilla Smith
  Funerals – June 8, 1991 – Felton R. Buckholtz II
  Funerals – June 17, 1991 – Amae Crane Thurman
  Funerals – August 14, 1991 – Ethel Evans Page
  Funerals – August 30, 1991 – William Henry Modster
  Funerals – September 14, 1991 – Lucille Elizabeth Jackson Williams
  Funerals – October 9, 1991 – Mark Lee Stephens
  Funerals – October 16, 1991 – Roger “Buddy” Welton
  Funerals – November 2, 1991 – Edwin Smith
  Funerals – November 6, 1991 – Julia Pauline Simpson
  Funerals – November 16, 1991 – Cenaca Von Gretchen Benton
  Funerals – December 21, 1991 – Horace W. Johnson, Jr.
  Funerals – December 31, 1991 – Cornell Washington, Jr.
  Funerals – January 10, 1992 – Lottie May Kinsey
  Funerals – February 26, 1992 – Esnold Walls Ruffin
  Funerals – February 29, 1992 – Venye Luke Corporal
  Funerals – April 9, 1992 – Frances A. Ragin
  Funerals – August 21, 1992 – Flavius B. Rowell, Jr.
  Funerals – August 26, 1992 – Lanneau Lloyd White, Jr.
  Funerals – August 31, 1992 – Damon Sidney Thomas
  Funerals – September 10, 1992 – Homer Boyd, Sr.
  Funerals – September 11, 1992 – Edwynia Ione Davis
  Funerals – October 21, 1992 – Charles Jones, Jr.
  Funerals – October 31, 1992 – Lela Fay Walsh
  Funerals – November 21, 1992 – Vida Brown
- Funerals (1993-1998 and nodate)
  Funerals – January 30, 1993 – Julia DePasse
  Funerals – December 18, 1993 – David Denton
  Funerals – June 4, 1994 – Johnnie Ruth Batts
  Funerals – July 21, 1994 – Rubye Louise Lathen
  Funerals – September 14, 1994 – Alzue Arlington Thompson
  Funerals – December 29, 1994 – Kelly Calhoun Richards, Sr.
  Funerals – June 13, 1995 – Beatrice M. Edgeton
  Funerals - June 13, 1995 – John E. Warren
  Funerals – June 24, 1995 – Emeline Hamilton Uter
  Funerals – July 11, 1995 – Mary Dell Bullen
  Funerals – October 3, 1995 – Helen Patterson
  Funerals – October 21, 1995 – Zoe Kim Norwood Ladd
  Funerals – October 23, 1995 – Charles Emerson Brown, Jr.
  Funerals – November 8, 1995 – Anita Laverne Seabron Dawson
  Funerals – December 7, 1995 – William Dabney Thompson
  Funerals – February 22, 1996 – Ross Matthew Miller, Jr.
  Funerals – March 9, 1996 – Gary Eugene Bernstein
  Funerals – March 1996 – Willie Zeadean Seymour Crenshaw
  Funerals – November 2, 1996 – Burton L. Woods
  Funerals – November 11, 1996 – Leonard L. Haynes
  Funerals – December 7, 1996 – Kathryn M. McDaniels
  Funerals – December 9, 1996 – Gertrude Jean Soso
  Funerals – March 15, 1997 – William L. Waters
  Funerals – October 1, 1997 – Marcelite M. Smith
  Funerals – October 8, 1997 – Marion Elizabeth Freeman
  Funerals – November 24, 1997 – Gwendolyn Hall
  Funerals – December 27, 1997 - Willie Clark, III
  Funerals – April 9, 1998 – Leona Steele
  Funerals – May 27, 1998 – Perry B. Freeman
  Funerals – July 13, 1998 – Frances Wimberly
  Funerals – August 1998 – Joyce S. Fiske
  Funerals – September 5, 1998 – Earl Newman
  Funerals – September 12, 1998 – Robert Williams Drye
  Funerals – October 15, 1998 – Granville Hillen Marshall
  Funerals – December 2, 1998 – Samuel Alexander Poe
  Funerals – December 28, 1998 – Mamie Doss Richards
  Funerals – December 30, 1998 – Helen E. Batiste
  Funerals – no date – Cleophus C. Bruce
  Funerals – “Be To Me a Rock of Refuge”
  Funerals – “A Dependable Source of Life”
  Funerals – “The Mark of a Christian”
- Sermons (1974-1975)
  Sermons – July 7, 1974 – “Jesus’ Inaugural”
  Sermons – August 11, 1974 – “Turning Trouble Into Hope”
  Sermons – August 25, 1974 – “A Divine Walloping”
  Sermons – September 1, 1974 – “Body Religion”
  Sermons – September 8, 1974 – “Soul Religion”
  Sermons – September 15, 1974 – “What You Know Can Hurt You”
  Sermons – September 29, 1974 – “Making the Most of What You Have”
  Sermons – October 6, 1974 – “What the World Needs Now”
  Sermons – October 20, 1974 – “The Effect of Righteousness”
  Sermons – November 3, 1974 – “Stealing in the Name of the Lord”
  Sermons – November 10, 1974 – “On Being True to My Native Land”
  Sermons – November 17, 1974 – “On Building Your Own House”
  Sermons – November 24, 1974 – “What Does it Mean to be Saved?”
  Sermons – November 28, 1974 – “Survival and Hardship”
  Sermons – December 1, 1974 - “In The Darkness God’s Voice”
  Sermons – December 15, 1974 – “Where is He?”
  Sermons – December 22, 1974 – “Christmas is Everybody’s Birthday”
  Sermons – 1974 – “You Are as Gods”
  Sermons – February 2, 1975 – “The Human Family is our Business”
  Sermons – February 9, 2014 – “The Sit-In Among the Shut-Out”
  Sermons – February 12, 1975 – “Of Being Merciful on Loving Mercy”
  Sermons – February 16, 1975 – “Whatever Became of Sin?”
  Sermons – March 16, 1975 – “Why Did Jesus Die?”
  Sermons – March 30, 1975 – “Find Life Among the Living”
  Sermons – April 6, 1975 – “Easter The New Exodus”
  Sermons – April 13, 1975 – “Overcoming the Moment of Danger”
  Sermons – April 20, 1975 – “Behold I Show You a Mystery”
  Sermons – April 27, 1975 – “What Are Our Real Intentions?”
  Sermons – May 4, 1975 – “And a Little Child Shall Lead Them”
  Sermons – May 11, 1975 – “Mothering To Heal a People”
  Sermons – June 1, 1975 – “On Trusting God”
  Sermons – June 22, 1975 – “On a Clear Day You Can See Forever”
  Sermons – July 6, 1975 – “And Underneath The Everlasting Arms”
  Sermons – July 13, 1975 – no title
  Sermons – July 27, 1975 – “Christian Discipleship in a Secular World”
  Sermons – August 3, 1975 – “The Lord’s Supper and Money”
  Sermons – August 31, 1975 – “Lift Up Concerns Before Hand”
  Sermons – September 7, 1975 – “Saying to God, ‘Thanks’.”
  Sermons – September 14, 1975 – “More Than Security”
  Sermons – September 21, 1975 – no title
  Sermons – October 5, 1975 – “Food For Life’s Trip”
  Sermons – October 12, 1975 – ‘Where Christ Labors (The Whereabouts of Christ)”
  Sermons – October 19, 1975 – “The Ingredients for a Just World”
  Sermons – November 9, 1975 – “A Tough Faith For a Tough Age”
  Sermons – November 16, 1975 – “Jesus’ Somber Command Reviewed”
  Sermons – November 30, 1975 – “A Personal Mood for Advent”
  Sermons – December 7, 1975 – “For the Person Who Has Everything”
  Sermons – December 14, 1975 – “God is Able”
  Sermons – December 21, 1975 – “Looking For Christmas”
  Sermons – December 24, 1975 – “The Manger and the Cross”
  Sermons – December 31, 1975 – “A Mood and a Faith for Watchnight”
  Sermons – 1975
- Sermons (1976)
  Sermons - - January 4, 1976 – “If you Get Where You’re Going Where Will You Be?”
  Sermons – January 11, 1976 – no sermon included
  Sermons – January 18, 1976 – “Put Out Into The Deep”
  Sermons – January 25, 1976 – “You Can Change The World”
  Sermons – February 1, 1976 – “Lord’s Supper is a gigantic act of consecration”
  Sermons – February 8, 1976 – no sermon included
  Sermons – February 15, 1976 – “Let Us Never Turn Back”
  Sermons – February 22, 1976 – no sermon included
  Sermons – February 29, 1976 – no sermon included
  Sermons – March 3, 1976 – “Able to Die, Willing to Live”
  Sermons – March 7, 1976 – “Your Influence For Christ”
  Sermons – March 14, 1976 – “Our Illustration on Father’s Day is a Man”
  Sermons – March 21, 1976 – “Life is God’s Gift to You”
  Sermons – April 4, 1976 – no sermon included
  Sermons – April 11, 1976 – “A Great Time to Witness”
  Sermons – April 15, 1976 – “There on the Cross:
  Sermons – April 18, 1976 – “God Prevails, We Shall Overcome”
  Sermons – May 2, 1976 – “When Your Children Ask”
  Sermons – May 9, 1976 – “Only The Strong Survive”
  Sermons – May 16, 1976 – “The Home: As Sign of the Kingdom”
  Sermons – May 23, 1976 – “Worship as Drama”
  Sermons – May 30, 1976 – “The Human: Itself a Sign of Eternal Life”
  Sermons – June 6, 1976 – “All The More….The World Needs the Gospel”
  Sermons – June 20, 1976 – “A Father’s Choice”
  Sermons – June 27, 1976 – Christ: The Bridge Over and Through Troubled Waters”
  Sermons – July 4, 1976 – “Considering This Most Unique Day”
  Sermons – July 11, 1976 – “Learning The Language of Love”
  Sermons – July 18, 1976 – “The Prodigal Brother”
  Sermons – September 5, 1976 – “God Is For Real”
  Sermons – September 12, 1976 – “Making Our House Our Home”
  Sermons – September 19, 1976 – “If You Mean It, Act Like It”
  Sermons – September 26, 1976 – “Remember Who Your Are”
  Sermons – October 3, 1976 – “The ‘A’, ‘B’, ‘C’ of Christian Faith”
  Sermons – October 17, 1976 – “Salvation and Economic Justice”
  Sermons – October 24, 1976 – “Hangin In Tough”
  Sermons – October 31, 1976 – no title
  Sermons – November 7, 1976 – “The Struggle of Integrity Towards Victory”
  Sermons – November 21, 1976 – “Only For The Young At Heart”
  Sermons – November 25, 1976 – “God Be Praised”
  Sermons – November 28, 1976 – no sermon included
  Sermons - December 5, 1976 – “A Communion Meditation”
  Sermons – December 12, 1976 – “Love Overthrowing Fear”
  Sermons – December 24, 1976 – “To Feel The Sugar Plums”
  Sermons – December 26, 1976 – “The Mood of Christmas, The Unlimited Mood of Christmas”
- Sermons (1977)
  Sermons – January 2, 1977 – “If You Give What You Are Giving What Will You Have Given”
  Sermons – January 16, 1977 – “MLK as Illustration of Commitment”
  Sermons – January 23, 1977 – “What is Your Religion About?”
  Sermons – February 6, 1977 – “You Can Be a New Person”
  Sermons – February 20, 1977
  Sermons – February 27, 1977 – “The Cross and Life’s Dailyness”
  Sermons – March 6, 1977 – “Even The Criminals”
  Sermons – March 27, 1977 – “Father Into Thy Hands, I commit my Spirit”
  Sermons – April 10, 1977 – “Easter A Call To Life”
  Sermons – April 24, 1977 – “Ear, Thumb, and Toe Religion”
  Sermons – May 1, 1977 – “Knowing the Risen Christ”
  Sermons – May 8, 1977 – “A Vision of Womanhood”
  Sermons – May 15, 1977 – “The Enormous Power of a Single You
  Sermons – May 22, 1977 – “It Takes Lots of Loving”
  Sermons – June 5, 1977 - “Freeway For The Presence Of God”
  Sermons – June 19, 1977 – “The Parable of the Impatient Father”
  Sermons – June 26, 1977 – “Rebel For The Most”
  Sermons – July 3, 1977
  Sermons – July 10, 1977 – “If We Do Not Lose Heart”
  Sermons – July 24, 1977 – “What’s Right With The Church?”
  Sermons – August 7, 1977 – “The Urgency of Giving”
  Sermons – August 14, 1977 – “God’s Untiring Confidence”
  Sermons – August 21, 1977 – “The Core of Christianity”
  Sermons – August 28, 1977 – “Winning Your Own Spurs”
  Sermons – October 2, 1977 – “Whose Kingdom Anyway”
  Sermons – October 16, 1977 – “When You Praise God”
  Sermons – October 23, 1977 – “What You Can Do For Peace”
  Sermons – November 13, 1977 – “A Woman’s Place”
  Sermons – November 27, 1977 – “Conquering The Enemy Within”
  Sermons – December 4, 1977 – “Conquering The Enemy Without”
  Sermons – December 11, 1977 – “If Christ Has Come to You, Jesus is not Coming Again”
  Sermons – December 18, 1977 – “You Don’t Have to do Anything”
  Sermons – December 24, 1977 – “Who Knows His Name?”
  Sermons – December 25, 1977 – “You Can Do Everything”
- Sermons (1978)
  Sermons – January 1, 1978 – “If You Become Who You’re Becoming Who Will You Be”
  Sermons – January 15, 1978 – “When You Look at King What Do You See”
  Sermons – February 5, 1978
  Sermons – March 5, 1978 – “What Do You Say About Him”
  Sermons – March 12, 1978 – “The Crucifixion: Miscalculations”
  Sermons – April 30, 1978 – “Walking Tall”
  Sermons – May 21, 1978 – “My Family Is The Human Race”
  Sermons – May 28, 1978 – “Is Anyone Else Up There?”
  Sermons – June 4, 1978 – Three Dimensions of a Moving Faith”
  Sermons – June 18, 1978 – “Go Home Slaves, Go Home”
  Sermons – June 25, 1978
  Sermons – July 2, 1978 – “A Vision For Holman”
  Sermons – July 9, 1978 –“What Kind of Soil Are We”
  Sermons – July 23, 1978 – “What Do You Seek From God?”
  Sermons – August 13, 1978 – “The Bottom Line”
  Sermons – August 27, 1978
  Sermons – September 17, 1978 – “God’s Unimaginable Heart”
  Sermons – October 22, 1978 – “Where Are Love’s Limits
  Sermons – November 5, 1978
  Sermons – December 24, 1978 – “God’s Strange Glory”
- Sermons (1979)
  Sermons – January 28, 1979
  Sermons – February 11, 1979
  Sermons – March 4, 1979 – “Stir What You’ve Got”
  Sermons – March 11, 1979 – “Living Nobly In Evil Days”
  Sermons – March 18, 1979 – “Any of us Can Become a Drop Out”
  Sermons – April 1, 1979 – “Staying in Love With Christ”
  Sermons – April 8, 1979 – “The Cross: God, With You, Prevailing”
  Sermons – April 15, 1979
  Sermons – April 22, 1979 – “The Two Hands of our Easter Faith”
  Sermons – May 6, 1979 – “Moving in a Great Dimension”
  Sermons – May 13, 1979 – “On What Do We Depend?”
  Sermons – May 20, 1979
  Sermons – May 27, 1979 – “When in Turmoil, Consecrate Your Life”
  Sermons – June 3, 1079 – “What the Spirit Can Do For You?”
  Sermons – June 17, 1979 – “Putting Your Life on the Line”
  Sermons – June 20, 1979 – “Jacob, Dream, Ladder”
  Sermons – June 24, 1979 – “Are We Shrinking Back or Making Life Our Very Own?
  Sermons – July 1, 1979 – “God’s Claim on our Money”
  Sermons – July 8, 1979 – “Three Things We Ought Not Do”
  Sermons – July 15, 1979 – “Healing is God’s Will For you”
  Sermons – August 5, 1979 – “A Divine Call To Our Age”
  Sermons – August 12, 1979 – “Every Man a Christ”
  Sermons – September 16, 1979 – “I Have Strength Enough for Anything Through Him Who Give Me Power”
  Sermons – September 23, 1979
  Sermons – September 30, 1979 – “Learning What is Pleasing to God”
  Sermons – October 7, 1979 – “Take This and Share It”
  Sermons – October 14, 1979 – “How to Share Your Friend”
  Sermons – October 21, 1979 – “Learning to Sing a New Song” (About Justice and Peace)
  Sermons – November 4, 1979 – “God Knows Your Name”
  Sermons – November 11, 1979 – “Why Are We Afraid to Say Good Bye?”
  Sermons – November 18, 1979 – “Done Made My Vows To The Lord”
  Sermons – November 22, 1979
  Sermons – November 25, 1979 – “Balancing The Two Urges Of Life”
  Sermons – December 2, 1979 – “Looking Ahead”
  Sermons – December 9, 1979
  Sermons – December 16, 1979 – “Gifts Anyone Can Afford”
  Sermons – December 23, 1979 – “Get Lost In Wonder, Love and Praise”
  Sermons – December 24, 1979 – “And a Baby Shall Win”
- Sermons (1980)
  Sermons – January 6, 1980 – “We’ve Come This Far By Faith”
  Sermons – January 20, 1980 – “Who Are We?”
  Sermons – February 3, 1980 – “How Do You Know That You Are A Child of God?”
  Sermons – February 12, 1980 – “Antidote To Fear”
  Sermons – March 2, 1980 – “Excellence Through Discipleship”
  Sermons – March 16, 1980 – “Let Us Excel In Giving”
  Sermons – March 30, 1980 – “Going After Victory”
  Sermons – April 6, 1980 – “As The Father Sent Me, So I Send You”
  Sermons – April 13, 1980
  Sermons – April 27, 1980 – “Something Worth Dying For”
  Sermons – May 4, 1980 – “DO You Carry Your I.D.?”
  Sermons – May 11, 1980
  Sermons – May 18, 1980 – “Let Us Struggle With The Vision”
  Sermons - May 25, 1980
  Sermons – June 1, 1980 – “When We Get Into The Real And Living”
  Sermons – June 8, 1980 – “Let Us All Be Free in Christ”
  Sermons – June 15, 1980 – “How To Be A Saint In A Storm”
  Sermons – June 22, 1980 – “What Would You Place At The Central Point Of Christianity?”
  Sermons – July 6, 1980 – “What Kind Of People Should We Be?”
  Sermons – July 20, 1980 – “Righteousness Exalts, Sin Deprives”
  Sermons – July 27, 1980 – “Show Your Proof”
  Sermons – August 3, 1980 – “Do You Neglect Salvation?”
  Sermons – September 7, 1980 – “Cleansing The Wound”
  Sermons – September 14, 1980 – “Strength To Love”
  Sermons – September 21, 1980 – “We Are Called To Follow Jesus”
  Sermons – September 28, 1980 – “Three Senses Of Faith”
  Sermons – October 5, 1980 – “Participating With Christ”
  Sermons – October 26, 1980 – “Doing The Beautiful Thing”
  Sermons – November 2, 1980 – “Saving Jesus From Christmas”
  Sermons – November 9, 1980 – “Everyone Is Responsible”
  Sermons – November 27, 1980 – “How Do You Get That Way?”
  Sermons – December 21, 1980 – “We Still Need Christmas”
  Sermons – December 24, 1980 – “Are You A Missing Person?”
- Sermons (1981)
  Sermons – January 4, 1981 – “The Other Side Of Tomorrow”
  Sermons – January 11, 1981